<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hugo on bootlegNinja.space</title>
    <link>https://bootlegninja.space/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hugo on bootlegNinja.space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 20:02:54 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bootlegninja.space/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Update</title>
      <link>https://bootlegninja.space/blog/recent-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 20:02:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bootlegninja.space/blog/recent-update/</guid>
      <description>So it&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I posted an update on this blog. I guess it seems like I&amp;rsquo;ve been taking a break from coding, but that&amp;rsquo;s not exactly accurate. Before starting this site, I spent a lot of time looking at the many web design tools and decided that I wanted to use an SSG to create this blog.
I investigated all the major SSGs, Hugo, Gatsby, Jekyll, 11ty and more and decided that Hugo was the best for me as it seemed to have the shortest entry barrier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Elements to a Hugo a Blog</title>
      <link>https://bootlegninja.space/blog/adding-things-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bootlegninja.space/blog/adding-things-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve really enjoyed playing around with Hugo over the past few weeks and am now using it to build another site for my wife. That site is almost complete, which is why I haven&amp;rsquo;t really posted much in this site for a while. I have been playing around and adding several small things to this site though.
One very cool addition to the site has been a Disqus comment function. It was very easy to set up as part of the Hugo framework and really worthwhile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Building</title>
      <link>https://bootlegninja.space/blog/blog-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bootlegninja.space/blog/blog-building/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on this blog for some time now and I think it&amp;rsquo;s worthwhile to document what I&amp;rsquo;ve done so far, just in case it&amp;rsquo;s helpful for other people. I mentioned in a previous post that I&amp;rsquo;m building this site with Hugo static site generator. Initially I followed a tutorial from Zachary Wade Betz, on how to build a Hugo blog from scratch. The tutorial can be found here Hugo Tutorial and truly is a great way to get accustomed to the structure of Hugo and how to use it to build a great website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Update</title>
      <link>https://bootlegninja.space/blog/quick-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bootlegninja.space/blog/quick-update/</guid>
      <description>This is my first mini update of this blog. I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning more and more about Hugo to build out this website and feel like I&amp;rsquo;m getting the hang of it now. I think Hugo is a great, easy to access SSG that is incredibly powerful and so fast. The way it generates static sites is really quite incredible. I really like it. There has been a bit of a learning curve, and there are still plenty of things that I still don&amp;rsquo;t know how to do, but it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been anywhere near as complicated as I thought it would be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Real Post</title>
      <link>https://bootlegninja.space/blog/my-first-real-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bootlegninja.space/blog/my-first-real-post/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;m getting back into designing websites for fun. I started learning HTML, CSS and JavaScript several years ago through freecodeCamp and I really enjoyed it, but somehow got out of practice a few years ago.
When I had a need to build a few websites several years ago, instead of putting the web design principles that I had already learned, I decided to use WordPress. I built quite a few sites using WordPress and some themes, but I always felt that it was kinda cheating - not really web design.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>